<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data by Design. on Yieldmo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data by Design. on Yieldmo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yieldmo Ranked in the Top 10% of Fastest Growing North American Companies on Deloitte’s 2017 Technology Fast 500™</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/yieldmo-ranked-top-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/yieldmo-ranked-top-10/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo ranked number 45 on Deloitte’s Technology Fast 500™, the 500 fastest growing technology, media, telecommunications, life sciences and energy tech companies in North America. Yieldmo grew 3,657% between 2013 and 2016.
Yieldmo’s Founder and Chief Executive Officer, Michael Yavonditte credits this extraordinary growth to Yieldmo’s highly-engaging, customer-centric approach to advertising. Driven by the world’s only engagement analytics system, Yieldmo delivers its customers deep insights derived from proprietary, user-preferred ad formats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Engagement</title>
      <link>/resources/onengagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/onengagement/</guid>
      <description>At &amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull up a Side of Meatballs</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/pull-up-a-side-of-meatballs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/pull-up-a-side-of-meatballs/</guid>
      <description>Hello again from the Yieldmo A|B Testing Lab!
We just love how much brand marketers like our Pull format (GIF below) and how they’ve built creative specifically for the unit to truly take advantage of its sequential storytelling possibilities. With the increase in the number of campaigns utilizing the Pull format, the A|B Testing Lab decided to start experimenting to see if we could improve performance even more. And that’s when we thought about meatballs (being close to lunchtime may have helped too…).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case for View-through Attribution</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/the-case-for-view-through-attribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/the-case-for-view-through-attribution/</guid>
      <description>With 4-out-of-5 consumers relying on their mobile phone to shop for products, mobile devices remain a critical research tool. Mobile-optimized sites have increased the ease of mobile shopping, leading to higher percentages of eCommerce revenue coming from mobile each year. But while mobile has certainly enabled shopping to occur anywhere at any time, the consumer path-to-purchase remains non-linear and comprised of multiple touchpoints.
Consumers live in an omnichannel world that may expose them to a brand via a desktop display ad, allow them to explore that brand’s products on their mobile phone as they commute to work, and then complete the checkout process on their tablet two weeks later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Shoppers: Who Are They?</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/mobile-shoppers-who-are-they/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/mobile-shoppers-who-are-they/</guid>
      <description>The 2017 holiday shopping season is already breaking records, with mobile accounting for 33.1% of the $6.59B spent on Cyber Monday —a 39.2% increase from 2016. To understand this behavior, we dug deep into our extensive engagement database to reveal the truth behind what drives mobile shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Outcomes and Audiences in a (Mostly) Cookieless Mobile World</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/measuring-outcomes-and-audiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/measuring-outcomes-and-audiences/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo Dragonfly&amp;trade; enables more accurate campaign measurement and efficiency by powering our ability to attribute conversions (via a Yieldmo pixel placed on check-out pages, product pages, etc.) to Yieldmo ad exposures and our ability to analyze which audience segments drove the largest share of performance. Together, this information drives stronger campaign performance by making optimizations possible at multiple levels—audience, ad format, ad creative, specific ad placement, etc.
This technology is powered by a combination of mobile device identification techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formats</title>
      <link>/products/formats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 17:51:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/formats/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yieldmo Furthers Its Lead as the Largest Independent Mobile Marketplace in the U.S.</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/yieldmo-further-lead-mobile-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/yieldmo-further-lead-mobile-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Recently forged partnerships with publishers such as Intermarkets and tronc have furthered Yieldmo’s lead as the largest independent mobile marketplace in the U.S. Yieldmo’s premium inventory is comprised of more than 1,400 of the top mobile destinations that span e-commerce, sports, news, lifestyle and entertainment.
Recent publisher partnerships further Yieldmo’s lead as the largest independent mobile marketplace in the U.S.
According to comScore, Yieldmo has a verified actual reach of more than 141 million unique mobile visitors - roughly 80% of the addressable market in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/company/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/company/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights</title>
      <link>/products/insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/insights/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs</title>
      <link>/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>/company/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/company/leadership/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensed Formats</title>
      <link>/licensedformats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/licensedformats/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketplace</title>
      <link>/products/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/marketplace/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opt</title>
      <link>/privacy/opt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/opt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publisher Guidelines</title>
      <link>/docs/pub_guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/pub_guidelines/</guid>
      <description>( a ) Publisher must not obscure or reduce the visibility of (including by applying similar colors to font and background) any Ad.
( b ) Publisher shall not: (i) sell, rent, lease, sublicense, transfer or otherwise provide access to the Yieldmo Service, Ads or any portion(s) thereof or provide any copies thereof to any third party; (ii) alter, modify, copy, translate, reverse engineer, decompile or disassemble the Yieldmo Service, Ads or any portion(s) thereof, or create derivative works therefrom; (iii) breach, disable, modify, tamper with, develop or use any workaround to interfere with the proper working of the Yieldmo Service or any security measure used by the Yieldmo Service, or attempt to do any of the foregoing; or (iv) use a third party ad server to serve any Ads.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>