<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data by Design. on Yieldmo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data by Design. on Yieldmo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yieldmo Ranked in the Top 10% of Fastest Growing North American Companies on Deloitte’s 2017 Technology Fast 500™</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/yieldmo-ranked-top-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/yieldmo-ranked-top-10/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo ranked number 45 on Deloitte’s Technology Fast 500™, the 500 fastest growing technology, media, telecommunications, life sciences and energy tech companies in North America. Yieldmo grew 3,657% between 2013 and 2016.
Yieldmo’s Founder and Chief Executive Officer, Michael Yavonditte credits this extraordinary growth to Yieldmo’s highly-engaging, customer-centric approach to advertising. Driven by the world’s only engagement analytics system, Yieldmo delivers its customers deep insights derived from proprietary, user-preferred ad formats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just How Engaging Is The iPhone X?</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/engagement-on-the-iphone-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 16:00:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/engagement-on-the-iphone-x/</guid>
      <description>Despite its $1,000+ price tag, Apple’s iPhone X is flying off the shelves. From the moment it launched, Apple sold close to 3 million iPhone X devices in just 20 minutes, 2,500 units per second. With iPhone X devices flooding the market, we wanted to understand how the users of these devices are behaving and what this means for advertisers.
Our billions of data points, combined with our ability to discern device models, provided more than enough information from which to glean insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Shoppers: Who Are They?</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/mobile-shoppers-who-are-they/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/mobile-shoppers-who-are-they/</guid>
      <description>The 2017 holiday shopping season is already breaking records, with mobile accounting for 33.1% of the $6.59B spent on Cyber Monday —a 39.2% increase from 2016. To understand this behavior, we dug deep into our extensive engagement database to reveal the truth behind what drives mobile shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Engagement</title>
      <link>/resources/onengagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/onengagement/</guid>
      <description>At &amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case for View-through Attribution</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/the-case-for-view-through-attribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/the-case-for-view-through-attribution/</guid>
      <description>With 4-out-of-5 consumers relying on their mobile phone to shop for products, mobile devices remain a critical research tool. Mobile-optimized sites have increased the ease of mobile shopping, leading to higher percentages of eCommerce revenue coming from mobile each year. But while mobile has certainly enabled shopping to occur anywhere at any time, the consumer path-to-purchase remains non-linear and comprised of multiple touchpoints.
Consumers live in an omnichannel world that may expose them to a brand via a desktop display ad, allow them to explore that brand’s products on their mobile phone as they commute to work, and then complete the checkout process on their tablet two weeks later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Outcomes and Audiences in a (Mostly) Cookieless Mobile World</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/measuring-outcomes-and-audiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/measuring-outcomes-and-audiences/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo Dragonfly&amp;trade; enables more accurate campaign measurement and efficiency by powering our ability to attribute conversions (via a Yieldmo pixel placed on check-out pages, product pages, etc.) to Yieldmo ad exposures and our ability to analyze which audience segments drove the largest share of performance. Together, this information drives stronger campaign performance by making optimizations possible at multiple levels—audience, ad format, ad creative, specific ad placement, etc.
This technology is powered by a combination of mobile device identification techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formats</title>
      <link>/products/formats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 17:51:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/formats/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yieldmo Furthers Its Lead as the Largest Independent Mobile Marketplace in the U.S.</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/yieldmo-further-lead-mobile-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/yieldmo-further-lead-mobile-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Recently forged partnerships with publishers such as Intermarkets and tronc have furthered Yieldmo’s lead as the largest independent mobile marketplace in the U.S. Yieldmo’s premium inventory is comprised of more than 1,400 of the top mobile destinations that span e-commerce, sports, news, lifestyle and entertainment.
Recent publisher partnerships further Yieldmo’s lead as the largest independent mobile marketplace in the U.S.
According to comScore, Yieldmo has a verified actual reach of more than 141 million unique mobile visitors - roughly 80% of the addressable market in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/company/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/company/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertiser Guidelines</title>
      <link>/docs/ad_guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/ad_guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo strives to provide advertisements that add value to the user experience and that advertise quality products or services that are relevant to the audience of the websites participating in the Yieldmo network.
All advertisements must adhere to these guidelines, which are intended to preserve the integrity of the Yieldmo service. Adherence to these guidelines does not constitute approval for participation of advertising on the Yieldmo Service, as Yieldmo may amend these guidelines or remove advertisements at its sole discretion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copyright Policy</title>
      <link>/docs/copyright_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/copyright_policy/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo will respond to properly submitted notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with applicable law. In the event that a person or entity has a good faith belief that its content is being displayed on or through the Yieldmo Service in a manner that constitutes copyright infringement (such person or entity, a &amp;ldquo;Complainant&amp;rdquo;) and sends to Yieldmo a properly submitted copyright notice as indicated below, Yieldmo will investigate, and if it determines, in its discretion, that the material is infringing, Yieldmo will remove the content and may terminate the access of the user or customer who posted such Content to the Service in the case of repeat infringers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electronic Payment Terms</title>
      <link>/docs/payment_terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/payment_terms/</guid>
      <description>Agency agrees to pay Media Company for all charges to Agency&amp;rsquo;s account for any campaign which Agency commences through the User Interface and/or via any applicable IO, in accordance with this Agreement and with any Payment Plan selected by Agency as described below. Agency agrees to: (i) promptly update all information to keep Agency&amp;rsquo;s account and Payment Account (defined below) current, complete and accurate (such as a change in billing address or e-mail), (ii) promptly notify Media Company in writing if Agency becomes aware of a potential breach of security, such as the unauthorized disclosure or use of Agency&amp;rsquo;s user name or password, and (iii) to comply with the agreements between Agency and the financial institution providing the Payment Account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights</title>
      <link>/products/insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/insights/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jobs</title>
      <link>/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>/company/leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/company/leadership/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensed Formats</title>
      <link>/licensedformats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/licensedformats/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketplace</title>
      <link>/products/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/marketplace/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opt</title>
      <link>/privacy/opt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/opt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publisher Guidelines</title>
      <link>/docs/pub_guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/pub_guidelines/</guid>
      <description>(a) Publisher must not obscure or reduce the visibility of (including by applying similar colors to font and background) any Ad.
(b) Publisher shall not: (i) sell, rent, lease, sublicense, transfer or otherwise provide access to the Yieldmo Service, Ads or any portion(s) thereof or provide any copies thereof to any third party; (ii) alter, modify, copy, translate, reverse engineer, decompile or disassemble the Yieldmo Service, Ads or any portion(s) thereof, or create derivative works therefrom; (iii) breach, disable, modify, tamper with, develop or use any workaround to interfere with the proper working of the Yieldmo Service or any security measure used by the Yieldmo Service, or attempt to do any of the foregoing; or (iv) use a third party ad server to serve any Ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retargeting Service Addendum</title>
      <link>/docs/retargeting_addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/retargeting_addendum/</guid>
      <description>In the event that Advertiser has selected the Yieldmo Retargeting Service, the following additional terms shall apply:
 The following definitions are added to the “Definitions” section of the Standard Terms. “Advertiser Data” means data that Media Company collects through Media Company Tags on the Properties, including any information that can be attributed to a user via cookies or other technologies that record events related to users’ activity on the Properties (such as the number of pages viewed, the products viewed, searches, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Terms of Use</title>
      <link>/docs/siteterms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/siteterms/</guid>
      <description>These Site Terms of Use, together with the Privacy Policy set forth at https://www.yieldmo.com/privacy/ (collectively, the “Agreement”) govern your access to and use of Yieldmo, Inc.’s website(s), including but not limited to its self-serve user interface and platform for the design and creation of ads known as AdBuilder (“AdBuilder”) and its user interface for advertising campaign management (the “User Interface”). These Terms of Use are a legally binding contract between the person or entity entering into this Agreement (“you”, or “your”) and Yieldmo, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>