<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Yieldmo</title>
    <link>/resources/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Yieldmo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/resources/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yieldmo Ranked in the Top 10% of Fastest Growing North American Companies on Deloitte’s 2017 Technology Fast 500™</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/yieldmo-ranked-top-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/yieldmo-ranked-top-10/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo ranked number 45 on Deloitte’s Technology Fast 500™, the 500 fastest growing technology, media, telecommunications, life sciences and energy tech companies in North America. Yieldmo grew 3,657% between 2013 and 2016.
Yieldmo’s Founder and Chief Executive Officer, Michael Yavonditte credits this extraordinary growth to Yieldmo’s highly-engaging, customer-centric approach to advertising. Driven by the world’s only engagement analytics system, Yieldmo delivers its customers deep insights derived from proprietary, user-preferred ad formats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engagement on the iPhone X</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/engagement-on-the-iphone-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/engagement-on-the-iphone-x/</guid>
      <description>Despite its $1,000+ price tag, Apple’s iPhone X is flying off the shelves. From the moment it launched, Apple sold close to 3 million iPhone X devices in just 20 minutes, 2,500 units per second. With iPhone X devices flooding the market, we wanted to understand how the users of these devices are behaving and what this means for advertisers.
Our more than 300 billion data points collected monthly, combined with our ability to discern specific device models, provided more than enough information from which to glean insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Shoppers: Who Are They?</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/mobile-shoppers-who-are-they/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/mobile-shoppers-who-are-they/</guid>
      <description>The 2017 holiday shopping season is already breaking records, with mobile accounting for 33.1% of the $6.59B spent on Cyber Monday —a 39.2% increase from 2016. To understand this behavior, we dug deep into our extensive engagement database to reveal the truth behind what drives mobile shopping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case for View-through Attribution</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/the-case-for-view-through-attribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/the-case-for-view-through-attribution/</guid>
      <description>With 4-out-of-5 consumers relying on their mobile phone to shop for products, mobile devices remain a critical research tool. Mobile-optimized sites have increased the ease of mobile shopping, leading to higher percentages of eCommerce revenue coming from mobile each year. But while mobile has certainly enabled shopping to occur anywhere at any time, the consumer path-to-purchase remains non-linear and comprised of multiple touchpoints.
Consumers live in an omnichannel world that may expose them to a brand via a desktop display ad, allow them to explore that brand’s products on their mobile phone as they commute to work, and then complete the checkout process on their tablet two weeks later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Outcomes and Audiences in a (Mostly) Cookieless Mobile World</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/measuring-outcomes-and-audiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/measuring-outcomes-and-audiences/</guid>
      <description>Yieldmo Dragonfly&amp;trade; enables more accurate campaign measurement and efficiency by powering our ability to attribute conversions (via a Yieldmo pixel placed on check-out pages, product pages, etc.) to Yieldmo ad exposures and our ability to analyze which audience segments drove the largest share of performance. Together, this information drives stronger campaign performance by making optimizations possible at multiple levels—audience, ad format, ad creative, specific ad placement, etc.
This technology is powered by a combination of mobile device identification techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yieldmo Furthers Its Lead as the Largest Independent Mobile Marketplace in the U.S.</title>
      <link>/resources/blog/yieldmo-further-lead-mobile-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/blog/yieldmo-further-lead-mobile-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Recently forged partnerships with publishers such as Intermarkets and tronc have furthered Yieldmo’s lead as the largest independent mobile marketplace in the U.S. Yieldmo’s premium inventory is comprised of more than 1,400 of the top mobile destinations that span e-commerce, sports, news, lifestyle and entertainment.
Recent publisher partnerships further Yieldmo’s lead as the largest independent mobile marketplace in the U.S.
According to comScore, Yieldmo has a verified actual reach of more than 141 million unique mobile visitors - roughly 80% of the addressable market in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>